James F. McNulty Papers, 1925-2002
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 5: Photographs
  - Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives, 1983-1984 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—campaign, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—campaign, No Date (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—campaign, No Date (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—campaign, No Date (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—family photographs, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Geraldine Ferraro, No Date (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Foley, Tom, No Date (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Freshman Class, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Goldwater, Barry, No Date (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Irish dignitaries, No Date (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—miscellaneous, No Date (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—O’neill, Tip, No Date (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Portraits, No Date (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Portraits, No Date (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—President Madrid (Mexico), No Date (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Proofs, No Date (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Reagan, Ronald (President), No Date (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Ribbon cutting, Kolb Road, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Staff, No Date (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—VA hospital, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - Photographs—U.S. House of Representatives—Vice-President George Bush, No Date (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Series 3: Miscellaneous Photographs
    - Photographs—1983 Flood (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Photographs—AFB dedication, No Date (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Photographs—American Embassy, London, No Date (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Photographs—Arizona Alumnus, 1953 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Photographs—Arizona State Senate, No Date (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Photographs—Army, No Date (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Photographs—Babbitt, Bruce, No Date (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Photographs—Baseball (Boston Red Sox), No Date (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Photographs—Board of Governors, County bar, No Date (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Photographs—Board of Governors, State bar, No Date (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Photographs—Board of Regents, No Date (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Photographs—Boston Latin Public School, class reunion, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Photographs—Boston Latin Public School, class reunion, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 28)
    - Photographs—Cochise Junior College, No Date (Box 88, Folder 29)
    - Photographs—Cochise Junior College—graduation, No Date (Box 88, Folder 30)
    - Photographs—Dedication, Apache Station, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 31)
    - Photographs—Democratic National Convention—Dukakis and Bentsen, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Photographs—Family, No Date (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Photographs—Frost, Robert, No Date (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Photographs—Kennedy, John F. and James McNulty, No Date (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Photographs—Law office, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Photographs—Mexico, No Date (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Photographs—Miscellaneous, Unidentified slides, No Date (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Photographs—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Photographs—Miscellaneous—Political, Unidentified slides, No Date (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Photographs—O’Connor, Sandra Day, No Date (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Photographs—Ordination of Father Clint Fowler, No Date (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Photographs—Party—Bisbee, AZ, No Date (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Photographs—Portraits, No Date (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Photographs—Postcards, No Date (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Photographs—Program for 62nd Birthday, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Photographs—St. Patrick’s day party—Dave Barnett, No Date (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Photographs—St. Patrick’s day party, No Date (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Photographs—School Friends, No Date (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Photographs—State Senate—Calendar, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Photographs—Udall, Morris, No Date (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Photographs—Udall, Stewart, No Date (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Photographs—University of Arizona—Commencement, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Photographs—University of Arizona—Commencement, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Photographs – Arizona Landscaps, No Date (Box 89, Folder 24)
- Subgroup 6: Newspaper clippings and scrapbook
  "Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks," is a collection of newspaper clippings documenting Jim McNulty’s life and career. Series One contains newspaper clippings dating from 1943-1997. Series Two consists of newspaper clippings collected during his stint in the U.S. House of Representatives (1981-1984). Series Three is a scrapbook created during the 1982 Campaign for the House of Representatives.
  - Series 1: Newspaper clippings, 1943-1996
    - Newspaper clippings, 1940-1949 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1950-1959 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings, January 1980-June 1980 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings, July 1980-August 1980 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings, September 1980-December 1980 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, February 1982-August 1982 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, September 1982-October 1982 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings, November 1982-December 1982 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings, March 1983-May 1983 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, June 1983-August 1983 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, September 1983-December 1983 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, January 1984 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings, February 1-9, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings, February 10-29, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings, March 1984 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, April 1-14, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, April 15-27, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, May 1-11, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings, May 12-23, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings, May 24-31, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings, June 1-13, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper clippings, June 13-21, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings, June 22-30, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings, July 1-15, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings, July 15-31, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings, August 1-15, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, August 15-31, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings, September 1984 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings, October 1-20, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings, October 22-26, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings, October 27-31, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, November 1-7, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings, November 8-December 1984 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings—University of Arizona, No Date (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper clippings—State Senate, No Date (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper clippings—State Senate reports, No Date (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, No Date (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper clippings—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper clippings—Miscellaneous, No Date (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper clippings—Delegation to the USSR, 1961-1962 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1985-1989 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1990-1997 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Series 2: U.S. House of Representatives, 1981-1984
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, January 1983 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, February 1983 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, March 1983 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, April 1983 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, May 1983 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, June 1983 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, July 1983 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, August 1983 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, September 1983 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, October 1983 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, November 1983 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, December 1983 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, January 1984 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, February 1984 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, February 1984 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, February 1984 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, March 1984 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, March 1984 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, April 1984 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, April 1984 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, May 1984 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, May 1984 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, May 1984 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, June 1984 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, June 1984 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, June 1984 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, June 1984 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, July 1984 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, July 1984 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, July 1984 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, August 1984 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, August 1984 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, August 1984 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, September 1984 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, September 1984 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives, October 1984-November 1984 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Series 3: U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, 1982 Campaign
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, p.1-30, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, p. 31-56, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, p. 57-79, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, p. 80-103, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Newspaper clippings—U.S. House of Representatives Scrapbook, miscellaneous clippings, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 17)
- Subgroup 7: Travel Slides, No Date
  Slides from travels to Russia, Canada and the Southwest.
  - Travel Slides from Russia, Canada and the Southwest, No Date (Box 97)
- Subgroup 8: Ephemera, 1949-1995
  Awards, certificates and memorabilia reflecting McNulty’s dedication to his profession, politics, the University of Arizona and the state of Arizona. This includes numerous plaques and trophies along with personal ephemera.
  - Bachelor of Law Diploma, May 30, 1951 (Box 98)
  - University of Arizona Alumni Association Distinguished Citizen Award, (Letter and Plaque), March 4, 1995 (Box 98)
  - University of Arizona A. L. Slonaker Bobcat Award, (Letter and Plaque), April 24, 1977 (Box 98)
  - McKale Memorial Dedication Program, November 30, 1973 (Box 98)
  - Dedication of the Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy, University of Arizona General Bulletin, #5, vol. XI, no. 3, Inscribed to Martin Gentry, July 1, 1940 (Box 98)
  - Distinguished Service Award, Arizona Electic Power Cooperative, (Plaque), April 9, 1991 (Box 98)
  - University of Arizona T. Bruce Huffman Memorial Letterman Service Award, (Plaque), November 11, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Honor from Sierra Vista City Council, (Plaque), No Date (Box 98)
  - Outstanding Service to Public Education, AZ Education Association, (Plaque), 1972-1973 (Box 98)
  - Award from the National Association of Mineral Institute Directors, (Plaque), May 1984 (Box 98)
  - “Proof that a Gentleman’s Gentleman isn’t always a valet” (Plaque), 1972 (Box 98)
  - Friend of 4-H, (Plaque), 1978 (Box 98)
  - Arizona-Mexico Border Health Foundation Award, (Plaque), October 1991 (Box 98)
  - Framed Lithograph Bank of Ireland, Dublin, No Date (Box 99)
  - Framed Lithograph, The Four Courts, Dublin, No Date (Box 99)
  - Guest Book from a dinner party with Majority Whip Tom Foley, September 21, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Congressional License Plates, No Date (Box 99)
  - Arizona Memorabilia, No Date (Box 99)
  - Graduation tassel and stole, No Date (Box 99)
  - Smoking pipes, No Date (Box 99)
  - Signature stamps, No Date (Box 99)
  - Business and membership cards, No Date (Box 99)
  - Arizona Alpha presidential gavel, No Date (Box 99)
  - University of Arizona Centennial Medallion for Distinguished Alum, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Eagle Scout Eagle Banquet trophy, 1983 (Box 99)
  - Bisbee Centennial Coin, 1977 (Box 99)
  - Unidentified plaque with signature, No Date (Box 99)
  - University of Arizona Homecoming 1975, 25th Anniversary of Track Team (Plaque) (Box 99)
  - Outstanding Service to the University of Arizona Athletic Program, (trophy), 1971 (Box 99)
  - University of Arizona Radio Quiz Champion, (trophy), 1949-1950 (Box 99)
  - Pen and ink sketch of Law Office of Gentry, McNulty, Desens and Behrens, Bisbee Arizona by Pat Pollock Rhoads, May 22, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Founding Fellow, Arizona Bar Foundation, (Plaque), February 1985 (Box 100)
  - Excellence in Leadership award, Valley Telephone Cooperative, Inc., (Plaque), 1990-1991 (Box 100)
  - Unidentified framed photo with numerous signatures, No Date (Box 100)
  - Certificate from the Clerk of the Arizona Supreme Court certifying McNulty as counselor in the State Supreme Court of Arizona, October 19, 1951 (Box 100)
  - Unframed pen and watercolor “Award of Merit” in recognition of election, Fernando Designs, November 2, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Campaign Posters “Jim McNulty Democrat U.S. Senate” and Papal Blessing document with photo of Pope, 1991 (Tube Tube)
- Subgroup Nine: Audiovisual Material, 1976-1984
  Materials are presented in KCS20, UCA20S, MBU18S, MBU-15S, BCS-20, 197 BCA-60, KCA60, UCA60, VHS, audiocassette tape, 45 rpm record, Quadruplex videotape and various reel-to-reel audio recordings. Formatting is noted where possible. The final box in this subgroup is almost exclusively audio material. These materials seem to be primarily concerned with Jim McNulty’s political career.
  - 1st Flight, KCS20, March 13, 1976-March 20, 1976 (Box 108)
  - Phoenix, Tape #1, MBU 15S, June 7, 1980 (Box 108)
  - Phoenix, Tape #2, MBU 15S, June 7, 1980 (Box 108)
  - Teacher’s Banquet Nighttime, #1, MBU 18S, August 1, 1980 (Box 108)
  - Teacher’s Banquet Nighttime, #2, MBU 18S, August 1, 1980 (Box 108)
  - La Placita #1, UCA 20S, August 9, 1982 (Box 108)
  - La Placita #2, UCA 20S, August 9, 1982 (Box 108)
  - La Placita #3, MBU 18S, August 9, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Douglas, Tape #1, MBU 18S, August 25, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Double Tree #1, MBU 18S, September 17, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Double Tree #2, MBU 18S, September 17, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Double Tree #3, MBU 18S, September 17, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Nogales, MBU 18S, September 21, 1982 (Box 108)
  - K of C, MBU 18S, September 21 1982 (Box 108)
  - Douglas Bisbee, MBU 18S, September 25, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Bisbee, MBU 18S, September 25, 1982 (Box 108)
  - Douglas Interviewing, MBU 18S, September 25, 1982 (Box 109)
  - Water, Plus: Dupnik and Jacquie McNulty, MBU 18S, October 20, 1982 (Box 109)
  - Jacquie McNulty (continued), MBU 18S, October 20, 1982 (Box 109)
  - Flood Marana #1, MBU 18s, October 4, 1983 (Box 109)
  - Flood Marana #2, MBU 18s, October 4, 1983 (Box 109)
  - Flood Marana, KCS20, October 4, 1983 (Box 109)
  - V.A. Hospital #1, MBU 18s, February 14, 1984 (Box 109)
  - V.A. Hospital #2, MBU 18s, February 14, 1984 (Box 109)
  - Small Bus Conference, MBU 18s, February 17, 1984 (Box 109)
  - New Members Caucus, BCS-20, March 21, 1984 (Box 109)
  - “A Day in the Life of…” Tape #1, BCA-60, April 10, 1984 (Box 109)
  - “A Day in the Life of…” Tape #2, BCA-60, April 10, 1984 (Box 109)
  - Interviews- Denise, Lee Smith, Mr. Ruiz, UCA 20s, August 22, 1984 (Box 109)
  - Interviews, MBU 18s, August 29, 1984 (Box 109)
  - San Manuel, MBU 18s, September 25, 1984 (Box 109)
  - “Copper”, BCS-20, September 27, 1984 (Box 109)
  - Family- Tennis and Piano Scenes, BRKCS-20BRK, October 23, 1984-October 24, 1984 (Box 110)
  - News Conference #1, BRKCS-20BRK, October 25, 1984 (Box 110)
  - News Conference #2, BRKCS-20BRK, October 25, 1984 (Box 110)
  - Congressional District 5 Debate, VHS, October 25, 1984 (Box 110)
  - Campaign Spots, McNulty, Kolbe, BCA-60, 1984 (Box 110)
  - McNulty, MBU 18s, 1984 (Box 110)
  - 2nd and 3rd Flights, MBU 18S, 1984 (Box 110)
  - 2, MBU 18S, No Date (Box 110)
  - 1984 McNulty/Kolbe Debates, VHS, No Date (Box 110)
  - Answers by Jim, UCA20s, No Date (Box 110)
  - Answers #2, MBU 18s, No Date (Box 110)
  - Answers #3, MBU 18s, No Date (Box 110)
  - Campaign- Commercial Composite Reel, UCA-60, No Date (Box 110)
  - Entire McNulty TV Campaign, VHS, No Date (Box 110)
  - Kolbe Congressional Record TV Spot, UCA 20S, No Date (Box 110)
  - McNulty Profile, VHS, No Date (Box 110)
  - New Members Caucus- Night Shots- Building and Capitol, BCS-10, No Date (Box 110)
  - People Asking Question #1, UCA 20s, No Date (Box 111)
  - People Asking Question #2, UCA 20s, No Date (Box 111)
  - Portrait of America, “Arizona,” VHS, No Date (Box 111)
  - Reaction Shots from Questioners for Mr. McNulty, MBU 18s, No Date (Box 111)
  - San Manuel, MBU 18S, No Date (Box 111)
  - Slides #1, UCA 20S, No Date (Box 111)
  - Slides #2, UCA 20S, No Date (Box 111)
  - Speaking Indoor, MBU 18S, No Date (Box 111)
  - Supers Star Background, MBU 18s, No Date (Box 111)
  - Tucson VA Hospital and Small Business Conference, MBU 18s, No Date (Box 111)
  - Untitled, KCA60, No Date (Box 111)
  - VA Hospital, MBU 18S, No Date (Box 111)
  - Work Tape Audio, UCA 20S, No Date (Box 111)
  - For U.S. Senate, 2 30-Second Radio Spots, Reel-to-Reel, August 29, 1980 (Box 112)
  - #4, For Congress, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, 2 Track Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - #5, For Congress, Testimonials without Music and McNulty, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, 2 Track Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - #6, Steve Irwin of San Diego, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, No Date (Box 112)
  - #7, “A Day in the Life,” Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, FT Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - #8, “Floods” Revised, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, No Date (Box 112)
  - #9, McNulty Reading, Reel-to-Reel, October 20, 1984 (Box 112)
  - #10, “Endorsement,” Reel-to-Reel, 2 Track Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - #11, Star, Star/Citizen, Reel-to-Reel, 15 ips, 2 Track Mono, October 30, 1984 (Box 112)
  - #12, Slogan, Reel-to-Reel, 15 ips, 2 Track Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - #13, TV “Medicare,” Tails Out, Reel-to-Reel, September 29, 1984 (Box 112)
  - #14, “Health Care” TV/Radio Revised, Reel-to-Reel, 15 ips, No Date (Box 112)
  - #15, For Congress, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, FT, No Date (Box 112)
  - #16, For Congress, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, FT Mono (Heads), No Date (Box 112)
  - #17, “Balanced Budget” TV, Reel-to-Reel, 7.5 speed, 2 Track Mono, No Date (Box 112)
  - Tails, 15mm, No Date (Box 112)
  - Jim McNulty Supers Star VT-2, [Quadruplex videotape], August 28, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Untitled, [Quadruplex videotape], September 6, 1984 (Box 112)
  - “Floods” revised Audio, [Quadruplex videotape], September 13, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Day in the Life and Floods Revised, [Quadruplex videotape], September 14, 1984 (Box 112)
  - Jim McNulty Background VT-1, [Quadruplex videotape], No Date (Box 112)
  - McFarland Single, (45 rpm record), 1958 (Box 112)
  - Announcement, Cassette Tape, November 21, 1979 (Box 112)
  - Press Conference – Q and A Tucson and Phoenix, Audiocassette Tape, August 21, 1980 (Box 112)
  - Kiko Open Line, Audiocassette Tape, August 8, 1980 (Box 112)